http://www.ironaccents.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy & Security
This site is hosted by Shopify. They hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Shopify automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. Please see the Shopify Privacy Policy for more information about how Shopify uses this information.Our Commitment to PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to Iron Accents on our website. The personal information collected when you order products, make requests, or register to receive materials from our company is as follows
Name - Billing & Shipping
Address - Billing & Shipping
Email address
Phone number - Billing & Shipping
Credit/Debit Card Information
On direct ship orders you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are
Name
Address
Phone Number Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Shopify to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Shopify may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. The Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties. If you order product from our site or register with our website to receive information as well as updates on our new products and services, your email address is submitted to our mailing list. Our mailing list uses a double opt-in policy. You will be emailed a confirming notice that must be responded to before you will receive our email offers.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our Commitment to Children's PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. How You Can Correct Your Information You can correct your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us at info@ironaccents.com. How To Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 866-438-4766 or send us an email at info@ironaccents.com.
Subscribe Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
